Guide to the Ephraim London papers,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: General, 1940s-1975
  - Subseries V.2: Entertainment, 1940s-1975
    - Samuel and Bella Spewack v. Metro-Goldwyn-Meyer, 1958-1975
      - Clippings--1958-1968 (Box 10, Folder 3)
      - Contracts--1950s-1960s (Box 10, Folder 4)
      - Correspondence--1967-1972 (Box 10, Folder 5)
      - Court Documents--1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 6)
      - Court Documents--1970-1975 (Box 10, Folder 7)
      - Depositions, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Exhibits, 1950s-1960s (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Legal Research, 1968-1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - A View from the Bridge, 1958-1961 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Subseries V.3: Personal, 1961-1975
    One small file in this subseries relates to London’s own work as an author.
    - Correspondence--1963-1975 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Lady Chatterley proposed by Ephraim London, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 6)